Madam.
After receiving the order,
Third Young Master has been kneeling outside all night.
He still hasn't left,
saying he must see you today.
Let him in.
Yes.
Mother.
Mother, please dismiss the attendants.
I have something to say.
Mother.
That Daoist priest's background is unknown.
Please let me investigate him thoroughly
before you make a decision.
This order
was given by your father.
I also want to help you,
but I'm afraid
there is no room for maneuver now.
Mother, you normally
know Father's mind best.
If you,
speak for me,
perhaps...
If I do that,
your father will surely detest me.
You really know how to
sow discord.
I wouldn't dare.
I am completely loyal to you.
I meant no such thing.
When I was eight,
I was humiliated in the academy.
Those sons of officials
pushed me into the snow
and insulted me,
calling me a servant's bastard.
It was you who appeared in time
and protected me behind you.
I still remember
what you said.
This child
will be of the Li family's bloodline from now on.
Whoever dares to touch him
will be making an enemy of my Qiwu Courtyard.
This kindness,
I remember every day.
Mother.
I know very well
that the women you and Father
chose for me
are all noble ladies.
But I
am already a cripple
who can hardly achieve my ambitions.
I don't seek fame or wealth.
I only want to find Qingcheng
and spend the rest of my life with her.
Please have pity on me, Mother,
and grant this marriage.
Mother.
Madam.
I thought
our Third Young Master
was just looking for a substitute for fun.
Now it seems
he has real feelings for her.
If Third Young Master
really cares for that Fang Qingcheng,
then that old card in your hand,
I'm afraid,
will not be as effective as before.
There is one thing
he reminded me of.
A merchant's daughter,
no matter what,
can't turn the world upside down.
Even if he really falls for her,
they'll be easy for us to control.
If he uses marriage
to connect with a noble lady,
gains their support,
and coaxes the Commander into favoring him,
then we'll be in real trouble.
I have built up
a lot of old grudges against him
and his lowly mother.
We can never let him have a chance to turn the tables.
What about the Commander?
Over the years, the Commander
has increasingly believed in divination.
Tell the Grand Diviner
to find an excuse
and come to the mansion immediately.
Yes.
Dear Zhuozhuo,
I have left Kuizhou tonight as promised.
I hope when we meet again,
there will be no more shackles in your heart.
Follow your heart.
Take care.
Jiaojiao.
Granny.
Tell me.
If there were no Zuirong Sect,
would Kuizhou
be a completely different place?
Mind your words, Miss.
If someone else hears this,
you could lose your head.
Over the years,
I've been trapped in the identity of Qingcheng.
But I am Fang Zhuozhuo,
not Fang Qingcheng.
If there were really no such dogmas,
maybe I could really
follow my heart.
Miss.
Never mind.
I was overthinking.
How can anyone in this world
truly do whatever they want?
I was daydreaming.
Let's eat.
Okay, let's eat.
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry.
What are you doing?
Put everything down.
Fang Zhuozhuo,
what are you up to now?
I just went to check the Qionghua seeds.
They are withering.
If we don't think of a way, they will die.
Do you know that Qionghua can't tolerate foul air?
Besides, I've never heard Mother say this.
Look at these flowers.
We water them every day,
but they wither more each day.
There are some strange trees in this world.
Before they break the soil,
they must first devour the surrounding life force.
I guess Qionghua is like that.
There is no record of planting Qionghua.
If we don't take a risk this time
and just plant them as before,
you,
me,
and the whole mansion
will hardly survive.
My lady, the flowers.
Do you want to trust me this once?
Hurry,
plant them all back.
Quickly plant all these flowers around the Qionghua.
Someone come!
Master.
Prepare some food and drinks.
Yes.
The kitchen was preparing ingredients for the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I saw some ready-made ones,
so I took the liberty of steaming them.
They're not as good as Granny Lan's.
Have a cup of tea.
You've worked hard.
No matter how good the cook is,
it's not the same taste as before.
How is your letter of divorce
coming along?
I might have to disappoint you, my lady.
That Taoist's appearance was suspicious.
Although it took some effort,
I still found
the Taoist's clothes
in a dark shop in the black market.
Besides the clothes,
there were also some women's daily necessities.
Today, I went to pay my respects to my father
and happened to run into the Grand Diviner coming to see him.
I had my doubts,
so I asked for another divination.
Guess what the result was, my lady.
Judging from your expression,
it must be a very good omen.
Your cousin's birth chart
and mine are an auspicious sign together.
Not only can it increase the luck of the Langjun Mansion,
but it will also help the fortune of Kuizhou.
My father was overjoyed to hear this
and immediately withdrew his order.
The young mistress of my Langjun Mansion
will probably be none other than your cousin.
Chu Shengyi.
Maybe my cousin's life
is worth nothing to you.
But to me,
she is the most important person.
It broke ground.
As promised,
when the Qiong flower blooms,
Qingcheng appears.
You're so smart, Young Master.
You knew Lady Fang would come to steal the flower tonight,
so you sent Lady Li's guards away in advance.
I was about to move the flower to Qiwu Courtyard.
Tonight is her last chance.
She stayed up for three nights
to fix the bracelet for me.
I promised her the Qiong flower,
so I should keep my promise.
The poison from this Qiong flower rouge
is getting stronger.
Even if I succeed this time...
Miss.
I've lost the tails.
The place you found
is indeed a good hiding spot.
On the day of the preliminary selection for the Makeup Ceremony,
Chu Shengyi will definitely set a trap.
It's his best chance to strike.
But if he fails to catch Qingcheng,
he will definitely take his anger out on me again.
As for Langjun Mansion,
I'm afraid we won't be able to return for a while.
How is the rouge making going?
This is my first time making it,
so I still need to experiment.
The proportions
might still need adjusting.
The transformation duration of the rouge
is getting shorter and shorter.
Is it because there is not enough Qiong flower?
I will try again.
The preliminary selection of the Makeup Ceremony
is only three days away.
Hurry up. Let's go.
Hurry.
The Master of Peixi Pavilion
has arrived.
The Master of Linlang Pavilion
The Master of Xiangyun Pavilion has arrived.
The Master of Yanzhi Pavilion.
You can't forfeit.
The competition is about to begin.
Since the Master of Yanzhi Pavilion is absent,
her qualification is revoked.
Why hasn't the Master arrived yet?
Wait.
I, Fang Qingcheng, am late.
Please forgive me, Chief Dian.
Lady Li has ordered.
Spring brings blooming flowers.
Please show your skills
using flowers as the theme
to paint the elegance of Kuizhou.
Yes.
Fang Qingcheng is here as expected.
Where Qionghua appears, Qingcheng follows.
Interesting.
Give the order.
Once the preliminary ends,
arrest her immediately.
Yes.
Fang Qingcheng,
in order to save Xin'er,
I am sorry.